<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-01-05T01:15:25.778Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-01-05T01:15:25.778Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Async Callbacks in JavaScript...Without Callbacks?]]></title>
        <id>61d392f6d2d9de084285b76f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-async-callbacks-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T23:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noodling about on Discord today, the same question came up a few times on a few different servers. I thought it was a great question, and it seems my brain doesn't work quite the way others might expect.  Here's the question: "So I have a fetch function, and I'm doing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Better Git Commit Messages – A Step-By-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>61d1c911a700150888933fb8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-better-git-commit-messages/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T22:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When first introduced to Git, it's typical for developers to feel uncomfortable with the process.  You might feel uncertainty when encountering the Git commit message, unsure how to properly summarize the changes you've made and why you've made them. But the earlier in your career you can develop good committing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open Visual Studio Code From Your Terminal]]></title>
        <id>61d3917cd2d9de084285b707</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-open-visual-studio-code-from-your-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T21:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we'll go over how you can open the VS Code text editor (Visual Studio Code) from your Mac terminal.  Opening your text editor from your terminal is a quick, easy way to open up new projects and begin coding faster.  How to Download and Open VS CodeThe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should CSS Override Default Browser Styles?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359880</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/should-css-override-default-styles/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T19:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS overrides can change the default look of almost anything:
You can use CSS to override what a checkbox or radio button looks like, but if you don’t, the checkbox will look like a default checkbox on your operating system 
…
Should CSS Override Default Browser Styles? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Tag in HTML – What is Metadata and Meta Description Example]]></title>
        <id>61c1ad52755c160824908a23</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/meta-tag-in-html-what-is-metadata-and-meta-description-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T18:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn what meta tags are in HTML and how to use them. Then we'll go over some of the most important meta tags that you need to include in every new HTML project.  Let's get started!  How to set up an HTML project When setting up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of Software Development Training – New Data for Choosing the Best IT Career Training Resource]]></title>
        <id>61d22dd0a700150888934505</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-software-development-training-new-data-for-choosing-the-best-it-career-training-resource/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T17:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long, long time ago – back in late November, 2021 to be precise – I wrote "A Data Analysis of IT Career Training Tool Efficacy" to help with the difficult task of making smart career education choices.  Believe it or not, there have already been some important updates. That article began]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Beautiful Box Shadows in HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>61d1a886a700150888933e3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-beautiful-box-shadows-in-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T16:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever you're designing a card in HTML, box shadows play a vital role in making the cards stand out.  Whether its a pricing page card or even an e-commerce product listing card, box shadows can make or break the look and the entire message that that cards need to convey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Git Works Under the Hood]]></title>
        <id>6176cded33422e07df363fa2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-under-the-hood/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T16:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, we all use some form of version control system, and the most popular one is Git.  A lot of us use Git, but very few know how it really works under the hood. We mostly just use it with a GUI client or the ones built into our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Search Functionality to a Frontend Application]]></title>
        <id>61c05f65aabf6478ea746281</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-search-to-frontend-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T16:28:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software developer, part of your job is to deliver the best user experience possible to those using your site or product.  And building a helpful and efficient search function is one way you can do this. So if you are looking for the right way to build out]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automount a Storage Partition on Startup in Linux]]></title>
        <id>61c55981755c16082490a553</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automount-a-storage-partition-on-startup-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T16:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By default, Linux OS does not automount any other partition at startup other than the root and the home partition.  You can mount other partitions very easily later, but you might want to enable some kind of automount feature on startup. This means that you won't need to mount them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Underlines Are Too Thin and Too Low in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359838</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-underlines-are-too-thin-and-too-low-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T15:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve encountered two bugs in Chrome while testing the new CSS text-decoration-thickness and text-underline-offset properties, and I want to share them with you here in this article.
But first, let’s acknowledge one thing:
Default underlines are inconsistent
Let’s add a …
CSS Underlines Are Too Thin and Too Low in Chrome originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetpack Features We Love and Use at CSS-Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360452</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jetpack-features-we-love-and-use-at-css-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T15:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
We use and love Jetpack around here. It’s a WordPress plugin that brings a whole suite of functionality to your site ranging from security to marketing with lots of ridiculously useful stuff in between! …
Jetpack Features We Love and Use at CSS-Tricks originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Workers Work in JavaScript – With a Practical JS Example]]></title>
        <id>61cfe874a7001508889339e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-webworkers-work-in-javascript-with-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T00:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will walk you through an example that will show you how web workers function in JavaScript with the help of WebSockets.  I think it's helpful to work with a practical use case because it is much simpler to understand the concepts when you can relate them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Based Fingerprinting]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360385</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-based-fingerprinting/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T21:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprinting is bad. It’s a term that refers to building up enough metadata about a user that you can essentially figure out who they are. JavaScript has access to all sorts of fingerprinting possibilities, which then combined with the IP …
CSS-Based Fingerprinting originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Browser Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359615</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-a-browser-extension/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T15:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll bet you are using browser extensions right now. Some of them are extremely popular and useful, like ad blockers, password managers, and PDF viewers. These extensions (or “add-ons”) are not limited to those purposes — you can do a …
How to Create a Browser Extension originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Kölker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composition-Based Design System In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/composition-based-design-system-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/composition-based-design-system-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma has advanced enough where it now supports some powerful concepts that can help with the flexibility and maintainability of a design system. In this article, Sasha explains why she finds the Systems Designer position so rewarding — and it’s not only because of how fast certain tools have developed to help her master challenges she faces in her work projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Aleksandra Nagornaia)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You (2021 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359698</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/thank-you-2021-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-01T17:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year has come to a close and it’s time again for our end-of-year wrapup. The most important message is this: thank you. (thankyouthankyou)
Thanks for stopping by and reading this site. If you didn’t, I’d be out …
Thank You (2021 Edition) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defensive CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360073</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/defensive-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T18:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed nails it again with “Defensive CSS.” The idea is that you should write CSS to be ready for issues caused by dynamic content. 
More items than you thought would be there? No problem, the area can expand or …
Defensive CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year, Fresh Desktop (January 2022 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2022/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What better way could there be to start the new year than with some fresh inspiration? Our collection of wallpapers for January 2022 is bound to put a smile on your face — and maybe spark new ideas, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Web is More Gooder, and Other Observations on Today’s Web Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359941</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-web-is-more-gooder-and-other-observations-on-todays-web-tech/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T20:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m actually working on a talk (whew! been a while! kinda feels good!) about just how good the world of building websites has gotten. I plan to cover a wide swath of web tech, on purpose, because I …
The Web is More Gooder, and Other Observations on Today’s Web Tech originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add Less]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359729</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/add-less/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T16:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re about to start a new website, what do you think first? Do you start with a library or framework you know, like React or Vue, or a meta-framework on top of that, like Next or Nuxt? Do you …
Add Less originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassidy Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Age DAM APIs to Simplify Your Media Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359708</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/new-age-dam-apis-to-simplify-your-media-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T16:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
High-velocity, online businesses produce multiple digital assets like banners, images, videos, PDFs, etc., to promote their businesses online. For such businesses, Digital Asset Management (DAM) solutions are essential. These solutions help centrally store, manage, …
New Age DAM APIs to Simplify Your Media Workflows originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageKit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empathetic Animation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=358975</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/empathetic-animation/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T16:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animation on the web is often a contentious topic. I think, in part, it’s because bad animation is blindingly obvious, whereas well-executed animation fades seamlessly into the background. When handled well, animation can really elevate a website, whether it’s just …
Empathetic Animation originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassie Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Yak Shaving and md-block, a new HTML element for Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359938</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-yak-shaving-and-md-block-a-new-html-element-for-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T16:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lea Verou made a Web Component for processing Markdown. Looks like there were a couple of others out there already, but I agree with Lea in that this is a good use case for the light DOM (as opposed …
On Yak Shaving and md-block, a new HTML element for Markdown originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Price Projects And Manage Scope Creep]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/how-price-projects-manage-scope-screep/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/how-price-projects-manage-scope-screep/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping, estimating, and running digital projects can often feel like an exercise in futility. In this article, Paul Boag explains why you need to start breaking your projects down into manageable phases and why that’s the best way to achieve significant benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add a Service Worker to Your Site]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359055</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/add-a-service-worker-to-your-site/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-28T16:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best things you can do for your website in 2022 is add a service worker, if you don’t have one in place already. Service workers give your website super powers. Today, I want to show you some …
Add a Service Worker to Your Site originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Ferdinandi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our favorite Chrome extensions of 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359860</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/our-favorite-chrome-extensions-of-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-28T16:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hadn’t heard of most of the Chrome extensions that Sarem Gizaw lists as 2021 favorites. Here are my hot takes on all of them, except the virtual learning specific ones that aren’t very relevant to me.
LoomOh that’s 
…
Our favorite Chrome extensions of 2021 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honor prefers-color-scheme in the CSS Paint API with Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359044</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/honor-prefers-color-scheme-in-the-css-paint-api-with-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the coolest things I’ve been messing with in the last couple years is the CSS Paint API. I love it. I did a talk on it, and made a little gallery of my own paint worklets…
Honor prefers-color-scheme in the CSS Paint API with Custom Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Gatsby Themes For WordPress-Powered Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/building-gatsby-themes-wordpress-powered-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/building-gatsby-themes-wordpress-powered-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you already built and published a Gatsby theme? In this article, Paulina Hetman explains how Gatsby themes work and what problems they can solve by comparing Gatsby themes with their WordPress counterparts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paulina Hetman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Custom Range Input That Looks Consistent Across All Browsers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/create-custom-range-input-consistent-browsers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/create-custom-range-input-consistent-browsers/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Range inputs have notoriously been a pain to style. Each browser renders the input differently requiring you to use vendor prefixes in order to create a cohesive look and feel. In this article, we’ll take a look at the quirkiness of the HTML range input and demonstrate how to style the input to look consistent across all major browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alyssa Holland)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful UX Guidelines, Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/tools-tips-resources-to-build-better-user-experiences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/tools-tips-resources-to-build-better-user-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A meaningful user experience is what can set your site apart from others. But what makes an experience truly meaningful? And how to achieve that? The tools, tips, and resources in this post not only help you to come up with a UX strategy that works for you and your team but also to circumvent potential UX pitfalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Core Web Vitals, A Smashing Magazine Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/core-web-vitals-case-study-smashing-magazine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/core-web-vitals-case-study-smashing-magazine/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve Core Web Vitals, a Smashing Magazine case study on how we detected and fixed the bottlenecks, and how we ended up with green scores, all the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Human-Machine Interfaces For Vehicles Of The Future]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/designing-human-machine-interfaces-future-vehicles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/designing-human-machine-interfaces-future-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern HMIs are transforming the way we interact with our vehicles. A car becomes a gadget that we use in a similar way as we use our phones. Users expect a lot of HMI, they even evaluate car experience based on the experience they have with HMI. In this article, let’s look at some ways to help us satisfy users’ needs with proper design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich &amp; Gleb Kuznetsov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billing Management For Your Next SaaS Idea Using Stripe And Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/billing-management-saas-stripe-azure-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/billing-management-saas-stripe-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In every software-as-a-service solution, user billing and payments are key aspects in the sale of services rendered. Let’s learn about Stripe and how the REST API can be programmatically used in serverless functions to manage the billing for an application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces: Defining Mobile Devices (Excerpt)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/touch-design-mobile-interfaces-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/touch-design-mobile-interfaces-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before we can talk about how people interact, much less how to take advantage of that knowledge and design, it’s important to understand a bit about the history, the technology, and what today counts as a mobile touchscreen device at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steven Hoober)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modifying Headers In HTTP(s) Requests In UI Automation Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/headers-https-requests-ui-automation-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/headers-https-requests-ui-automation-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be able to modify headers in a testing environment is a great thing to have. It allows control over your application as one can bypass authentication, set cookies, and so on. In this article, Nafees Nehar explores some methods which allow modification of headers in an automation testing setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nafees Nehar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Christmas Icon Sets And Vector Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/free-holiday-icons-vector-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/free-holiday-icons-vector-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody loves a nice freebie, right? To get you in the mood for the upcoming holidays, we collected some winter- and holiday-themed icon sets and vector elements that you can use in your projects for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Links For Websites And Emails: A Guideline]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/designing-better-links-websites-emails-guideline/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/designing-better-links-websites-emails-guideline/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are so many websites out there that have not considered the overall usability of their visually impaired users. When it comes to designing better links and sending better emails, Slava Shestopalov has a few tips on how to improve your website’s experience while accessibility in mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>